A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), News Clippings FA1856
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), News Clippings
1932-1988
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller family
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
FA1856
13.66 Cubic Feet 37 card file boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised of newspaper and periodical clippings which document activities, events, community affairs, contributions, political campaigns, philanthropic giving, and public perception of Rockefeller family members from 1932-1988. The clippings were compiled and maintained by staff of the Rockefeller family office (Room 5600), including materials that may have been compiled by the Rockefeller family Public Relations Department (1946-1982) as well as the family office library.
The majority of clippings pertain to Nelson A. Rockefeller's political endeavors. A small selection documents notable people outside the Rockefeller family, including but not limited to Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt and Pablo Picasso.
Arrangement
Arranged in original order, as received, with several alphabetical runs of personal names.
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr. - Laura Spelman Rockefeller (Box 1)
- John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller (Box 2)
- Decuevas - Anne C. Rockefeller (Box 3)
- Abby Aldrich Rockefeller - Harry Rockefeller (Box 4)
- Hope Rockefeller - Willard Rockefeller (Box 5)
- William Rockefeller - Winthrop Rockefeller, Jr. (Box 6)
- Bobo Rockefeller - John D. Rockefeller IV (Box 7)
- John D. Rockefeller IV - Laurance S. Rockefeller (Box 8)
- Laurance S. Rockefeller - Rodman C. Rockefeller (Box 9)
- Steven Rockefeller - Knustantin K. Rokossovsky (Box 10)
- ROL - Elliot Roosevelt (Box 11)
- Franklin D. Roosevelt - Nancy Hank (Box 12)
- Nancy Hanks - Charles H. Percy (Box 13)
- Pablo Picasso - David Rockefeller (Box 14)
- David Rockefeller - David Rockefeller Family (Box 15)
- David Rockefeller - Nelson A. Rockefeller Non-Political, 1966-1967; 1969 (Box 16)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1969-1970 (Box 16)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1968-June 1969 (Box 17)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1968-1973 December 12 (Box 18)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1973 December-1975 (Box 19)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1975 February-1976 April (Box 20)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1976 (Box 21)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1977-1979 (Box 21)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1979-1982 (Box 22)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1962-1963 (Box 22)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1963 February-1964 May (Box 23)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1964 May-1966 August (Box 24)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1966-1967 October (Box 25)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1967-1968 (Box 26)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1960 (Box 27, Box 28)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Non-Political, 1961-1962 (Box 28)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1962-1963 (Box 28)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1963 September-1964 January (Box 29)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1964 (Box 30)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics - Cartoons (Box 30)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1959 (Box 30, Box 31)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1958 October-1959 May (Box 32)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1958 October-1961 October (Box 33)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics, 1961 (Box 34)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Politics - Editorials, 1961-1962 (Box 34)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1951-1957 (Box 34)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Miscellaneous, 1944-1960 (Box 35)
  Scope and Contents
  Including speeches
- Nelson A. Rockefeller - Miscellaneous (Box 36)
  Including speeches and writings
- Mary Todhunter Clark Rockefeller, 1948-1962 (Box 36)
- Happy Rockefeller, 1963-1966; 1974-1982 (Box 37)